[
    
{ 

    "question": "What is the highest number known in mathematics?",
     "options": {
         "A": "1,000,000,000",
         "B": "9",
         "C": "10",
         "D": "Uncountable"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "How many fingers (in total) are there in hand?",
     "options": {
         "A": "1",
         "B": "3",
         "C": "5",
         "D": "10"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = 10"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What are the missing numbers in the sequence? 1 _ 3 _ 5 _ 6 _ 8 _ 10.",
     "options": {
         "A": "2, 4, 7, 9.",
         "B": "1, 3, 5, 10.",
         "C": "0, 1, 2, 3.",
         "D": "0, 2, 4, 9."
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What is the third number mathematics?",
     "options": {
         "A": "0",
         "B": "3",
         "C": "10",
         "D": "7"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Which of the following letters represents NORTH-EAST?",
     "options": {
         "A": "NE",
         "B": "SE",
         "C": "NW",
         "D": "SW"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "1, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 8, 13, 21 - Which one doesn't belong to this series?",
     "options": {
         "A": "1",
         "B": "2",
         "C": "4",
         "D": "13"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "121,144,169,196 ... What's next?",
     "options": {
         "A": "260",
         "B": "225",
         "C": "298",
         "D": "310"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Divide 20 by half and add ten. What did you get?",
     "options": {
         "A": "25",
         "B": "70",
         "C": "35",
         "D": "10"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "",
     "options": {
         "A": "",
         "B": "",
         "C": "",
         "D": ""
     },
 
     "answer": ""
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "2 + 2 X 2â€¦. What do you get?",
     "options": {
         "A": "4",
         "B": "6",
         "C": "8",
         "D": "10"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "How many seconds are there in 1hour?",
     "options": {
         "A": "120",
         "B": "2400",
         "C": "3600",
         "D": "60"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "How many grams make a kilogram?",
     "options": {
         "A": "10",
         "B": "100",
         "C": "1000",
         "D": "10000"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "If the length of a square is 5cm, find the perimeter of the square",
     "options": {
         "A": "5",
         "B": "20",
         "C": "10",
         "D": "50"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "An isosceles triangle has",
     "options": {
         "A": "Two equal sides",
         "B": "Three equal sides",
         "C": "All sides are not equal",
         "D": "None of the above"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "A hexagon is a",
     "options": {
         "A": "Five sided polygon",
         "B": "Four sided polygon",
         "C": "Six sided polygon",
         "D": "Seven sided polygon"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Round off to nearest whole number 129.89",
     "options": {
         "A": "129",
         "B": "129.8",
         "C": "129.9",
         "D": "130"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = D"
 }  

]